WILFREDO HERNÁNDEZ

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Passionate about new technologies with experience building full-stack web applications, designing cloud architectures, microservices, working with containers and serverless technologies. Experience working with SCRUM and KANBAN methodologies.

Autonomy, teamwork and adaptation to change, searching new challenges, learn and continuous improvement, special interest focused on increasing cloud skills and knowledge.

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Solutions Architect - Associate AWS SysOps Administrator - Associate AWS Developer - Associate **AWS Cloud Practitioner**

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - Comprehension C2 Expression B2

French - Comprehension B2 Expression A2

EXPERIENCE

UNIVERSIDAD EUROPEA DEL ATLÁNTICO

Web Developer

DIC 2019 - PRESENT

- Analysis and development of web components and SPA.
- Analysis, Design and development of REST APIs with Node.js.
- Architecture design of web projects and cloud native microservices.
- Task automation.
- Establishing development environments with Docker.

Technologies: Reactis, Typescript, Vuejs, AWS, Nuxt, Docker, GCP.

Web Builder

SFP 2018 - NOV 2019

• Built elements and web pages from prototypes, application of responsive styles and interactivity.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, Javascript.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSIDAD EUROPEA DEL ATLÁNTICO

2018 - 2022

Degree in Software Engineering

CONTACT



wilfredo.hernandez.ar@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/wilfredo-hndz



+34 656 374 207



github.com/Woohaik



stackoverflow.com/users/17200950/woohaik